<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aagr</title>
    <link>https://aagr.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on aagr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023-, Aman Agrawal; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aagr.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How My Raspberry Pi Blog Stays Online?</title>
      <link>https://aagr.xyz/posts/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aagr.xyz/posts/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>I recently implemented some behind-the-scenes changes to significantly increase the reliability and performance of my blog. Using the power of multiple Raspberry Pis and Cloudflare Argo Tunnels, I&amp;rsquo;ve set up load balancing and redundancy that will keep my blog up and running – even if things go wrong at home.&#xA;The Original Setup&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s step back and look at how things started:&#xA;Humble Pi Power: At its heart, my blog is powered by a tiny Raspberry Pi 4 tucked away in the corner of my home office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cocktails, Friends, Laughter</title>
      <link>https://aagr.xyz/posts/cocktails-2024-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aagr.xyz/posts/cocktails-2024-03/</guid>
      <description>Okay, buckle up, because I have a tale to tell. I, someone who usually orders the simplest possible drink at a bar, recently decided to throw caution to the wind and host a cocktail party. Armed with a shaker, some questionable recipes, and a healthy dose of hope, I embarked on a journey of amateur mixology.&#xA;Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing, it was actually&amp;hellip;a hit? Let&amp;rsquo;s just say the results may have been more influenced by a steadily-increasing blood alcohol content than genuine cocktail mastery, but who am I to complain?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new hobby!</title>
      <link>https://aagr.xyz/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aagr.xyz/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Scrolling through endless feeds of Instagram Reels and TikTok videos has become the norm – short bursts of entertainment that demand little attention and offer instant gratification. While I do enjoy the mindless fun from time to time, I&amp;rsquo;ve begun to realize that something&amp;rsquo;s missing. I long for a change of pace, something with more depth. That&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m turning to a more traditional outlet: blogging.&#xA;The thought of having a dedicated space to simply write for myself and for anyone who&amp;rsquo;s interested is incredibly appealing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://aagr.xyz/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aagr.xyz/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want to get in touch? I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you! Whether you have feedback on my blog, a project idea, or just want to say hello, I&amp;rsquo;m always happy to connect.&#xA;Shoot me a hi at me@aagr.xyz</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://aagr.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aagr.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! I&amp;rsquo;m Aman Agrawal, a software engineer bazed in buzzing London (UK) with a passion for exploring life&amp;rsquo;s little adventures with a quarter-life crisis!&#xA;This blog is my space to share the things that spark my curiosity. From the occasional tech musing to my haphazard experiments in the kitchen or reflections on everyday life, I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll find something here that makes you smile, think, or maybe even try something new.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
